This bail release was granted solely
on the confession of the murderer
the world is calling
the "Witch of the Century."
While we respect the court's decision,
our official stance
is that we cannot accept it.
Are you saying you can't accept it
because it's the confession of a criminal?
Just because she's a criminal?
We're talking about the murderer
you called the "Witch of the Century."
The one you all
couldn't stop calling a psychopath.
Uh, what if, just as you believe,
that woman schoolteacher who was just
recently released really is the killer?
Isn't it too dangerous
to have her out there among our citizens?
You mentioned "what if,"
but that's exactly the thing
we're most worried about.
The court also acknowledged the risk
and ordered an electronic ankle monitor
as the minimum safeguard.
Let me remind you,
Ms. An was actually sentenced
to life in prison in her initial trial.
The trial was fairly conducted
and was strictly
based on admissible evidence,
without the slightest deviation.
The prosecution will do everything
in its power
to ensure these two criminals
never make a mockery
of the Korean justice system again.
Thank you.
Will Prosecutor Baek Dong-hun
remain in charge?
I heard there are rumors.
His investigation methods
are rather heavy-handed
because of his background
in the police force.
As a prosecutor,
he has an unshakable sense of principle.
Of course, we are aware
of the public criticism he's facing.
But we'll make it absolutely clear
that our investigation was not in error.
How do you plan to move forward with…
LETTER OF RESIGNATION
Ah!
You're so damn arrogant.
Why are you getting ahead of yourself
when we didn't even dismiss you?
Just lay low in the CWCU for now.
It won't be easy there either.
Kids these days
commit the same crimes as adults.
And if you get some extra time,
you should put that relentlessness
of yours to work and keep digging.
On your own, that is.
On my own?
What? Would you prefer I say
"just for fun?"
If you find something solid,
you can let me know directly.
That's what you wanted.
If you understood, take this and get out.
Let's go.
You've got all these people on your side.
YUN-SU, START AFRESH!
MS. AN! STAY STRONG!
WE'RE WITH YOU
#REUNITE MOM AND DAUGHTER
GET LOST, HUSBAND KILLER
Uh… Oh.
What kind of sick people would…
MURDERER
These are the last ones.
All right?
Oh, uh,
I don't even know how to thank you.
Oh, not at all.
I just helped out a little. That's all.
All right.
No, no, no, Sop. Don't.
Oh.
Ms. An Yun-su?
- Oh. She's here already.
- Are you there?
- Oh, hello.
- Oh. Yes. Hello.
- Come in.
- You know what?
This place is right by the road.
I kept missing it and going in circles.
- I'm Ms. An Yun-su's attorney.
- I'm Bae Sun-deok.
- We spoke on the phone before.
- Right. Yeah.
Yeah.
Goodness.
Did I scare you?
Don't worry. I'm not a scary person.
- Huh?
- Sop.
Can you show me around your room?
- Hello, there.
- Hello.
Make sure to charge it
every night while you sleep.
Four hours of charging will give you
about 24 hours of use.
It's water-resistant,
but avoid soaking it in hot water
for too long, like at a public bath.
And since it sits
on a bony area like this,
it can cause some chafing.
Put on some lotion
right there every now and then.
Is that everything?
Now I'm going to install
the home monitoring devices.
Here. Please.
- Sign each of these.
- Okay.
Oh boy.
Uh, could… could you
maybe put that somewhere less visible?
Well, no.
It's going where we can get
the clearest view
and can monitor you at all times.
Any signal loss or power cut,
and you're the one who will be penalized.
You want me gone, don't you?
Still, you won't even offer me water?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'll get you some.
Should we discuss the rest outside?
Yes.
Paju and Ilsan.
You aren't ever allowed
to leave these areas.
If you ever need to,
you'll have to get approval first.
But of course,
it's ideal not to put yourself
in that position at all,
and we actually even extended your range
due to your daughter's commute
to kindergarten.
And, uh, yeah.
From 10:00 p.m. to 6:00 a.m.,
you're not allowed
to vacate your current residence.
The moment you open the front door
and take a few steps,
the control center will get an alert.
So basically,
I'm not allowed to do anything.
Oh, uh, a lot of people
make the mistake of thinking
that they're completely free
once they get out.
You're still a murder suspect, though,
so don't forget that.
You have to be very cautious, Ms. An.
And stay alert, always.
- Oh.
- Hey.
- What is it?
- Sop said she's hungry.
Oh, um, what would you like?
Hmm, Chapagetti.
Chapagetti? I'll make it in a minute.
- All right. I should get going.
- Okay.
Okay, let's see.
Hey, here you go. You want some chocolate?
Oh.
- Huh?
- Uh…
She doesn't really like sweets.
Oh, I see.
Bye.
- Come on.
- Go ahead.
Well, I'd better get going now.
Uh, if it's okay, would you…
would you like to stay for dinner?
Oh, I'm fine. I've got things to do.
Still, though,
you probably didn't eat lunch.
You should enjoy
a quiet meal with Sop today.
See you later.
- See you. Goodbye!
- Good night, then.
- Good night.
- Yeah.
Bye.
I told you.
I keep all the ramyeon in the corner.
Go with Sop.
I'll make it.
Here.
Wait.
Well, I went to the shared cells first,
and the water cooled down.
Could you request meds for me?
What?
You know you have to consult
with the medical officer first. Right?
I haven't been able to sleep at night.
Right.
C… Can you… let…
And could you bring a newspaper for me?
This evening's would be even better.
Um, I'll ask the supervisor.
Appreciate it.
- The paper.
- Okay.
Can you, please? Yeah.
You like it that much?
Yes, I'm enjoying it.
Here, drink some water while you eat.
You're speaking so politely now.
I am.
Here, sweetie.
It's great that now you're speaking
a little more formal,
but I liked it better before
when we were like friends.
You finished?
Should we go brushy-brushy now?
Come on.
I'm sorry.
I guess Sop's asleep. Yeah?
Sorry.
I know I have already hurt your feelings.
And, yeah, I'm apologizing
to make myself feel better too.
But I still wanna apologize.
You know what? Just hit me.
I know it won't make you feel better
all of a sudden,
but if you think it'll help
even just a little…
I'm sorry, Yun-su.
I'm really, really sorry.
I brought tteokbokki
from Mi-suk's on the way.
What about beer?
Of course I did.
You're the one
who painted the walls, right?
I made my husband do it.
And you got the groceries?
Well, Sop never skips breakfast, you know?
Oh, and I took your car
to the repair shop.
They mentioned it needs more work
than they thought.
You can pick it up tomorrow
or the day after.
- Mm.
- Oh, the cab's here.
Hey, go inside. Oh.
- No, just leave it. I'll clean it up.
- Oh God. Hold on.
- Hey, you should get inside now.
- It didn't have to get here so fast.
Hey, come on. Go inside.
If Sop wakes up,
and you're not there, she'll get scared.
Give her a big hug before you go to sleep.
Mm.
I'll see you.
Your husband?
I'll confess
to killing him.
But not for free, of course.
FEMALE SCHOOLTEACHER "A" RELEASED ON BAIL
There's something
I need you to do for me too.
There's
someone I didn't get to kill that day.
When you get out of here…
I want you to kill that person for me.
ILSAN DENTIST COUPLE MURDER
Just one! Let me just ask one question!
Just one! The victims had a son.
Do you have anything at all
to say to the boy who you left an orphan?
As I'm sure you know, little boy,
your mom and dad weren't such good people.
Your crime is being their child,
and now you're paying for it too.
If it's for your daughter…
you'd do anything, wouldn't you?
HOTPICK'S TOP-RANKED STORY UNPACKED:
THE ILSAN DENTIST COUPLE MURDER CASE
VICTIMS' SON, FIRST REPORTER AND WITNESS,
WAS AT THE SCENE OF CRIME
How do you want to die?
Please. Please help me.
I have to!
- Hello.
Sop, slow down. Don't forget your bag.
- Hi!
- Hi there!
- Here's Sop's bag.
- Oh.
- Move!
Please don't take it personally.
She's just excited
to visit with her friends again.
No, I'm grateful
to see her smile like that.
I'm happy to see you.
It's really great to see you around again,
and Sop too.
Thank you for your kind words.
- Sop, you forgot your bag.
- You lose.
Rock, paper, scissors.
You won.
Hello.
Attention, shoppers.
Our fresh kimchi is now on special.
Just 4,000 won a jar. Pick up some today
in the refrigerated section…
Hey.
- Gosh, really?
- Oh wow.
- No way.
- It's her.
Jesus.
Yeah.
That's 26,500 won.
Oh.
I'm sorry.
People look at me in one of two ways.
Either with caution or with curiosity.
It feels like the whole world even knows
how many times a month
I slept with my husband.
People offer you sympathy and support
when you're just a distant figure.
But when you're suddenly
right in front of them,
they can't help feeling
scared and curious.
You knew this could happen.
Yeah.
So when is my trial on appeal?
It's set for three weeks from now.
Three weeks?
The prosecution seems to be
rushing things.
It seems they're not going to back down.
They're going to tear you apart
and drag your name through the mud.
Well, I won't just take it sitting down.
Hmm.
And I will find out who murdered
my husband, no matter what.
All right, but
the killer confessed already.
Uh, that woman?
She can't be trusted.
If she suddenly starts denying it--
I don't plan to rely on
just her confession alone.
I'm gonna find proof that you're innocent
and that you didn't murder your husband.
It was her.
Inmate 407, the meds you requested.
Confirmed.
Another public defender.
They refused your case.
Said it was for personal reasons.
That's the fourth one now.
I just
thought you should know.
What can I get you?
Their yukgaejang's really good.
Yeah, yukgaejang, please.
I'll have janchi-guksu.
All right.
How's it feel to be out?
Somehow, you look skinnier.
I heard you transferred
to another department.
This, just out of curiosity?
Sure know how to make
people uncomfortable.
I like it when
people feel like that around me.
It makes my job easier.
You're quite the show-off, aren't you?
Ms. An Yun-su.
Yes, Prosecutor Baek Dong-hun.
You're still a primary murder suspect.
If you're uncomfortable, it's not me.
It's the situation.
What makes you so certain
that it was me?
What do you even know?
That's what I want to believe.
Thanks for the food.
Long time no see.
It's been quite a while, Ms. Eom.
I thought you stopped taking
public defense cases
after becoming a professor.
Yeah, well, somehow,
I ended up back here again.
I was actually wishing
you would come back around for this one.
But it won't be an easy one for you.
Yeah, well, I kinda figured as much.
Let's go.
JIN YOUNG-IN, PROFESSOR/ATTORNEY
I heard everyone is avoiding me.
So why did you step up to defend me?
I guess I did volunteer, but
I don't know that "stepped up"
is the right way to put it.
To be honest,
my wife suggested it.
She said your confession
gave an innocent person a chance
to clear her name,
and I agreed with her.
Do you…
think that my confession is real?
I should, shouldn't I?
Well, some people don't think it is.
The prosecutors don't believe it.
I can see why. They're prosecutors.
And there are the ones who simply
come here to boost their careers.
Am I
being interviewed right now?
Or are you trying
to wear me down or something?
I'm not.
If I had some personal agenda,
I would've gone to Ms. An Yun-su.
And so we're clear,
I already have a solid career.
Let me ask you now.
Can I trust you, Ms. Mo Eun?
Can I trust you?
Sure.
Ms. Eom,
it looks like Inmate 407
is writing a letter.
Shouldn't we go check?
Censoring letters is against the law.
And besides, Mr. Jin would never let us.
Please give this to An Yun-su.
If it's related to the trial,
it could result in problems later.
Do you mind if I ask what it's about?
You're going to read it anyway.
What?
It's exercise time soon.
Can we wrap this up?
It's the only time I see the sun.
Yeah.
So you're still in solitary, aren't you?
I'll make arrangements
to get you in the general block.
It won't be immediate,
but it should be by next week, I think.
I wasn't expecting that.
I appreciate it.
I guess you really liked this lawyer.
You talked to him for a long time.
Didn't you?
That's because I heard
he wrote a book recently.
Can you get me a copy?
Uh, 180. Which…
Who said you were allowed
to sit there, bitch?
Hey, Pudgy.
- Hey!
- Huh?
I told you, you weren't supposed to let
just anyone sit here, didn't I?
Oh.
You're not supposed to sit there.
You're not gonna get up?
What? Got a fuckin' issue?
No.
Wow, look at this bitch. Fuckin' little--
Oh, you…
Don't mess around with her.
What's with the whispering?
Oh, forget it. Just keep walking.
Why? Who the hell is she?
That's the Witch.
Her?
Damn it.
She looks like a fuckin' joke.
CITY GAS SAFETY INSPECTION NOTICE
PICK UP SOP
- Hi, Ma!
- No. No.
I'm sorry I'm late.
- I'm so sorry, ma'am.
- Oh.
You can ask me to watch her
from time to time.
I really enjoy spending time with Sop.
I appreciate it. Take care.
Sop, did you say bye to the teacher?
- Goodbye.
Good girl.
- Mom.
- Huh?
Where are we going?
We're going home, honey.
Get some sleep, okay?
I got a call from Mo Eun's lawyer.
Apparently, she left a letter for you.
He's coming to my office tomorrow.
I was thinking, "Please, someone,
anyone, take her case," and now…
Oh, whoa. Here it is.
I mean, I never imagined
it'd be Jin Young-in. Oh.
This is him.
He hit the ground himself,
taking on cases even the police ignored
'cause the victims
were all poor and powerless.
Reading this and his last book,
I thought, "Wow, could I ever
do something like that?
He even got thank-yous from his clients.
They made me really jealous, to be honest.
Hello, Mr. Jin.
Oh, you're here?
Yeah, yeah. That's okay. Park there.
We're on the second floor. Uh-huh.
All right. He's here.
Wow, he drives a nice car.
Man, and he's got a beautiful wife too.
He spent ten years as a public defender
and handled over a thousand cases.
He's an expert.
So why would someone like that take on--
Don't worry.
He'll be able to ease
some of your anxiety.
Trust me.
She wrote it on the spot
during our consultation.
She just kept writing.
Seemed like she had a lot to say.
Did you… read the letter by any chance?
No, I didn't read it.
Ah, trust is the most important thing
between a lawyer and their client.
I'd never read it
without permission.
I should get going.
I'll get in touch with you
through Mr. Jang.
Thanks very much.
Thank you for today. Take care.
Oh, about that letter.
Please tell me
if there's anything suspicious.
We don't want it to cause trouble
for the trial.
Okay, I will. I'll get going. Goodbye.
- See you.
- Bye.
The COVID-19 pandemic.
What would you say is the biggest change
that it brought to our society?
Well, there were many changes,
but what really stood out
was the rapid rise
of contact-free activities following
the implementation of social distancing.
Even after those measures were lifted,
people were still used
to this contact-free lifestyle.
Yun-su.
How's life on the outside?
Are you enjoying your time
with your daughter?
Even though I'm in prison,
I'll always be watching over you
and rooting for you,
no matter where you are
or what you're doing.
I heard that your trial
will be in three weeks.
I hope the preparations are going well.
I am planning to take the stand
as a witness.
I'll tell the truth
with a repentant heart.
I sincerely hope you'll be able
to walk out of that courtroom
with a smile on your face.
Who are you?
Sop.
Sop! Sop!
Open your eyes, please.
Sop!
Sop! Sop!
Open your eyes. Sop! Sop! Please.
…mental health issues
have also become a major concern.
What are your thoughts
on this social phenomenon?
COVID-19 brought
a lot of psychological stress for many.
With self-isolation and social distancing,
more and more people…
According to a mental health survey
by the Ministry of Health and Welfare,
about 38% of the population
have experienced depression
due to COVID-19.
Yes, hello?
Oh, is something wrong?
You sound a little…
No, no, I was just… I was asleep.
Ah, did you read the letter?
Yeah, I read the letter.
Can I ask you what it said?
She says she'll be a witness in my trial.
Oh, really?
Says she'll tell the truth
with a repentant heart.
Oh.
The rest was
just asking how I was doing.
Oh, that's a relief.
Sorry for bothering you so late.
Good night.
Night.
Look, right there.
NIGHT CURFEW VIOLATION
AN YUN-SU
This is Bae Sun-deok.
What?
An Yun-su?
By the way, Yun-su,
even if you do get out,
don't get any funny ideas.
Don't get caught up with emotion
and do something you can't afford,
like chasing after the truth.
Emergency! Emergency!
An inmate has escaped!
Because no matter where you are
or what you're doing,
I will always be watching you.